# **Adiel Goldin**

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

My passion for law started from an early age. Faced with the challenge of choosing between private and public law, both of which deeply fascinated me, I made the decision to enrol in a unique L.L.B. program in the Netherlands that specializes in both. This program exposed me to a variety of courses, from corporate law to technology regulation. All of these were done by approaching law through transnational, international and comparative lenses. What sets this academic program apart is its incorporation of sociological and social behavioural viewpoints, adding a holistic dimension to the study of law. Following my graduation, I translated this theoretical knowledge into practical experience by working in a law firm and the legal department of a satellite company in Singapore.

## WORK EXPERIENCES

# In-House Counsel (Internship), Kacific ☑

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023

· Skills developed: contract drafting, compliance assessments, and in-depth knowledge of corporate and finance law

Singapore, Singapore

• Led due diligence processes, assisted in debt restructuring, and managed regulatory compliance in over 25 markets

#### **Legal Intern,** August Law Corporation □

Aug 2023 - Sep 2023

• Skills developed: legal research, case analysis, and client communication

Singapore, Singapore

· Managed cases with a multi-jurisdictional nature, conducted legal research, and effectively coordinated attorneys and clients

#### **EDUCATION**

## L.L.B. Global Law (International Business Law Minor), Tilburg University

Sep 2020 - Jun 2023

Relevant modules: Corporate & Finance Law, Commercial Law, Public International Law, International Trade Law, and EU Law

Tilburg, Netherlands

## **A** EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

# Yuverta MBO Tilburg, Volunteer Teacher

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

• Skills developed: strong leadership, critical thinking and effective communication

Tilburg, Netherlands

• Facilitated discussions on diverse and existential topics such as human nature and the Israeli-Arab conflict, encouraging deep engagement and promoting critical analysis.

# Hashomer Hatzair, Youth Leader

Jan 2016 - May 2019

• Skills developed: group cooperation, honest communication, and the value of initiative and active participation.

Sofia, Bulgaria

• Organized events and lessons about global challenges using interactive activities and easyto-understand lessons to promote social awareness and historical education.

### (S) LANGUAGES

Hebrew

**English** 

Native

**Proficient** 

# **Bulgarian**

**Proficient** 

adieleligoldin@gmail.com 1/1